4online.tv 2011-12-04

# Privacy Policy | Online TV - Watch Live TV & Free Channels Broadcasting on the Internet

Welcome to **4online.tv** \- Live streaming TV, **Online TV** , broadband internet TV stations from all over the world.

**Privacy Policy for www.4online.tv**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@4online.tv.

At www.4online.tv, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.4online.tv and how it is used.

**What information do we collect ?**

We do not require that users provide any personally identifiable information to use our services. We don’t ask for personal information.

We may collect and use the following kinds of personal data: information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, operating system, referral source, length of visit, number of visitors and number of page views.

We never collect personally identifiable information about users such as names, e-mail addresses or telephone numbers.

Non-personally identifiable information such as IP address or browser type will be collected.

We collect statistics using Google Analytics, and these statistics include: number of users, page views, countries, languages, browsers, keywords searched. We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html .

This website does not deliver pop-up or spyware or viruses of any kind.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.4online.tv does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.4online.tv.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.4online.tv and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …. Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.4online.tv send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.4online.tv has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.4online.tv’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on our website.

You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

**Third party websites**

The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. This website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites. If you link to other websites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

To watch other channels, you simply select a country from the menu, and click a channel to begin watching.   
**Note: You can not watch OFFLINE channels online, we will update their status when the channels are live on Internet.**
